<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating My Company on Indalit Cloud Consulting</title>
    <link>http://www.indalit.com/tags/creating-my-company/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creating My Company on Indalit Cloud Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.indalit.com/tags/creating-my-company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating the Packs Web Page</title>
      <link>http://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/13/veronique-packs-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/13/veronique-packs-page/</guid>
      <description>As you probably don&#39;t know, I am creating/making/writing/configuring www.indalit.com using an open source static site generator called Hugo. I&#39;ve chosen a theme and moved forward from that. The small glitch is I&#39;m am NOT a web developer at all. I&#39;ve learned Python for fun and mostly forgot since I haven&#39;t been practicing, but that&#39;s all my experience in the development world. So working on this site has been a great challenge for me; Hugo provides a theme, but that&#39;s just the base, after that you have alot of modifications to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sort of Personal Blog</title>
      <link>http://www.indalit.com/blog/2017/10/01/veronique-personal-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.indalit.com/blog/2017/10/01/veronique-personal-blog/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s official, we are starting the process of creating our company. I assume this will take a few months, but I am not in a hurry. At this stage roles are not clear, so I go with the flow. For now, I seem responsible for the design/creation and configuration of our website Indalit.com and it&amp;rsquo;s content. So, I decided on having a blog. Inicially thinking it will look professional, be a good place to publish what I write about AWS and help with SEO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>