<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creating My Company on Indalit Cloud Consulting</title>
    <link>https://www.indalit.com/tags/creating-my-company/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creating My Company on Indalit Cloud Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 01:00:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.indalit.com/tags/creating-my-company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am an Accountant Now</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/03/23/veronique-the-accountant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 01:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/03/23/veronique-the-accountant/</guid>
      <description>Where I&amp;rsquo;m at At this stage, I&amp;rsquo;ve done things in a total crazy order. I&amp;rsquo;ve followed what I feel like doing instead of doing it all in the right order. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter, all things are moving forward, there might be some wasted time but at least I&amp;rsquo;m doing what I enjoy. Until&amp;hellip;
Veronique the Accountant This business is divided into two parts. The first one is this project, so you already have an idea what it&amp;rsquo;s about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/03/04/veronique-business-plan-directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/03/04/veronique-business-plan-directions/</guid>
      <description>My Business Plan Like any serious future business owner, one does a business plan. This may seem like a small thing, but it&amp;rsquo;s a crazy document to complete, which makes you write a bunch of other documents/excel sheets. You also need to do a market research which I honestly have been ignoring. But if you do all that correctly, then your business is sure to thrive. Once you have finished the business plan, all you need to do is push &amp;ldquo;PLAY&amp;rdquo; and it all happens because everything is ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrialized Versus Homemade</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/26/veronique-industrialed-versus-homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/26/veronique-industrialed-versus-homemade/</guid>
      <description>Ugliness After working on the website for over a week, maybe even two, I can&amp;rsquo;t help but find it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the right look. I&amp;rsquo;ve redone the packs page/pages a few times and I&amp;rsquo;m still not happy with them. I know I will have to continue working on them tomorrow. The homepage template is great, perfectly corporate, but the images in the carousel and the formatting of the text just don&amp;rsquo;t cut it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can&#39;t Imagine the Goal</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/25/veronique-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 01:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/25/veronique-the-end/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m continuing to be a web developer, graphic designer and writer. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely better at HTML and CSS, but not the design and content part. So I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to accept the not so perfect pages, they may not look top notch professional but they will do the job. In the end, what will matter is the service we give and not the design of our web site. As for content, I guess &amp;ldquo;INTERNET&amp;rdquo; will need to deal with the more direct approach and finally give up on all the bullshit keywords and phrases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Things Change</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/21/veronique-web-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/21/veronique-web-developer/</guid>
      <description>It’s time for another update. I’m still a web developer for now, it’s taking much more time than planned. The good news is yesterday I sat down and started to write HTML with nested DIVS and formatting all over the place without any hesitation, just came out like I’ve been doing it for some time. I know this won’t last, when I’m done, it will go away as fast as it came, but I’m proud of myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging www.indalit.com</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/18/veronique-debugging-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 00:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/18/veronique-debugging-website/</guid>
      <description>On my previous post I was working on www.indalit.com. First of all, I, innocent me, actually thought I was finished. But then, I made the mistake at looking at the page with my mobile phone!!! And then making my browser screen smaller!!! Wow, horrible. So, it turns out working with CSS and positioning correctly DIVs is just not a beginners thing. Took me hours of work. Now it works great, but my associate has decided it needs to be centered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating the Packs Web Page</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/13/veronique-packs-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2018/02/13/veronique-packs-page/</guid>
      <description>As you probably don&#39;t know, I am creating/making/writing/configuring www.indalit.com using an open source static site generator called Hugo. I&#39;ve chosen a theme and moved forward from that. The small glitch is I&#39;m am NOT a web developer at all. I&#39;ve learned Python for fun and mostly forgot since I haven&#39;t been practicing, but that&#39;s all my experience in the development world. So working on this site has been a great challenge for me; Hugo provides a theme, but that&#39;s just the base and after that you have a lot of modifications to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sort of Personal Blog</title>
      <link>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2017/10/01/veronique-personal-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.indalit.com/blog/2017/10/01/veronique-personal-blog/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s official, we are starting the process of creating our company. I assume this will take a few months, but I am not in a hurry. At this stage roles are not clear, so I go with the flow. For now, I seem responsible for the design/creation and configuration of our website Indalit.com and it&amp;rsquo;s content. So, I decided on having a blog. Inicially thinking it will look professional, be a good place to publish what I write about AWS and help with SEO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>